We are here at the Gaash beach, Israel, where Michael Lucas, a porn star from New York, is shooting his ‎new movie “Inside Israel”, a collaboration with Israeli stars. ‎
We came to watch
What are you doing here?
well we're shooting a porn scene
We are shooting two guys having sex and this amazing location. I love this Place Beach
Why are you shooting in Israel? -because I'm Jewish and I love israel very much
I come here people ask me "why do you go there?"
All that we see is West Bank and Gaza, West Bank and Gaza
Ruins. So through the porn movie actually you can see that this is a beautiful country
basically you're doing this movie for zionism
I'm a zionist but I'm doing this movie for tourism. Gay man a very good tourists
They have money and they spend it on themselves, so that's the way to bring them
‎‎(Jonathan Agassi – Israeli porn star): The plot is about me hosting a photographer who ‎comes from Spain
He arrives with a bunch of models. They are staying in my ‎apartment and together we go and hit the whole country.
We do a lot of a lot of fashion production, a lot of ‎shoots, a lots of.. sex ‎
‎-‎ Like "The English Patient". ‎
‎-‎ Only more successful. ‎
‎-‎ Say, as an Israeli, don’t you feel a bit ashamed to be in a movie like that? ‎
‎-‎ Ashamed, no. I am very proud and happy of what I do; I’m happy with what I do. It’s a job that you enjoy ‎any second of it. ‎
It was great, wonderful. It's the first time I did that on the sea and It's such a great experience
It was amazing
Very nice, nice views, very nice sea. The water was amazing, this guy was great
-Was it for real what we so?
- of course it was
- you're not cold?
- Sex warms up people!
‎-‎ What tricks do you need to do a good sex scene? ‎
‎-‎ First of all, you need to know your body; you have to know how to pose, where to pose. You ‎have to remain sexy.
Must make sure to do it all together. You Know, you also need to know ‎where the camera.
Not looking at the camera, but always know where the camera comes ‎from. So that’s pretty complicated, it’s harder than it seems. ‎
Israeli men versus International, other men - what's special about israeli men?
well, I think they are very sexy, very hot and I think they're very beautiful
‎-‎ So how does one become a porn star? ‎
‎-‎ It’s a lot of commitment. Lots and lots of commitment. A lot of going to the gym, familiarity ‎with a Big boss like Michael Lucas and you’ll succeed. ‎